Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
(SWORDS CLANGING)
(DOGS BARKING)
(RAVENS CAWING)
(THUDDING)
(GASPS)
(CAWS)
I've taken your castle.
Theon?
It's Prince Theon now.
Get up.
You have to get dressed.
I've taken Winterfell.
I took it.
I'm occupying it.
I sent men over the walls
with grappling
claws and ropes.
Why?
To take the castle.
You went with Robb.
And he sent me back to Pyke.
I'm a Greyjoy.
I can't fight for Robb
and my father both.
Where's Hodor?
I don't know.
Find the halfwit.
My men are bringing
your people together
in the courtyard.
Why?
So you and I can go
down and tell them
how you've yielded
Winterfell to me.
I won't.
Yes. you will.
I won't. I'll never yield.
We'll fight you
and throw you out.
(CLEARS THROAT)
The castle is mine.
But these people
are still yours.
You'll yield to
keep them safe.
to keep them alive.
That's what
a good lord would do.
Think carefully about
what you want to say.
Theon.
Did you hate us
the whole time?
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(HORSE WHINNIES)
I've yielded
Winterfell to Theon.
Louder.
Say Prince Theon.
I've yielded Winterfell
to Prince Theon.
You all know me.
Aye. we know you for
a steaming sack of shit.
Farlen. you be silent.
Listen to your
little lord. Farlen.
He has more sense
than you do.
All of you should
do as he commands.
My father has donned
the ancient crown
of Salt and Rock
and declared himself
King of the Iron Islands.
He claims the North as well
by right of conquest.
You are all his subjects.
Bugger that.
I serve the Starks.
If you think you can
hold the North with it...
Shut up!
THEON: If you serve me
as loyally as you served
Ned Stark.
I will be as good to
you as he ever was.
Steady.
Betray me. and you will
wish you hadn't.
(CROWD MURMURING)
Maester Luwin.
send a raven to Pyke
informing my father
of my victory here.
And one to Deepwood
Motte to my sister.
Inform her that she's to bring
500 men to Winterfell.
(CROWD MURMURING)
You are a maester
of the Citadel.
sworn to serve
the Lord of Winterfell.
are you not?
I am.
I am the Lord of Winterfell
as Bran just informed you.
Send the ravens.
My lord.
My Lord Greyjoy.
I see you've finally learned
how to address your betters.
What do you want?
I was brought here
a captive.
You were here
the day I was taken.
I'm the one who took you.
What of it?
Let me serve you.
THEON: Serve me how?
I need fighters.
not kitchen sluts.
It was Robb Stark who
put me in the kitchens.
Put a spear in my hand again.
So you can bury it in my neck?
Do you take me for a fool?
Get up.
Step aside.
Why?
It's your dream.
little lord.
The ocean has come
to swallow this place.
I ain't letting it drown me.
THEON: You'll all go about
your tasks as usual.
And in a few days' time...
RODRIK: Greyjoy!
We caught this one
on his way back from
Torrhen's Square.
Took out two of ours
before I got his sword.
Ser Rodrik. it grieves
me that we meet as foes.
It grieves me
you've less honor
than a back alley whore.
You were raised
here under this roof.
These people are your people.
They are not my people.
King Robb thought
of you as a brother.
My brothers are dead.
They died fighting
Stark men. men like you.
Aye. they died
fighting a war
your father started.
Lord Stark raised
you among his own sons.
Among them.
but not one of them.
I was his hostage.
taken from my home.
If he were
alive to see this...
He's not. He's dead.
The Seven Kingdoms are at war.
And Winterfell is mine.
I should have put
a sword in your belly
instead of in your hand.
You've served this house
faithfully. old man.
But keep talking and I'll...
(SPITS)
(GRUNTS)
Take him to the cells.
Lock him up...
My prince.
You cannot let that stand.
He must pay.
I'll lock him in
a cell until he rots.
No. he has to pay
the iron price.
They'll never respect you
while he lives.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
Ser Rodrik.
I sentence you to death!
No! You said no harm
would come to them
if I yielded.
The old man couldn't
keep his mouth shut.
I urge you not to make
a hasty decision.
THEON: He disrespected me
in front of my men.
That was his decision.
not mine.
He is worth more to you
alive than dead.
The Starks will pay.
Please. Theon.
think what you do.
You'll address
me as Prince Theon
or you'll be next.
Come.
No!
No! Theon!
BRAN: Rodrik!
He who passes the sentence
should swing the sword.
BRAN: (SOBBING)
I'm begging you.
RODRIK: Coward.
Stop. Stop!
Stop right now!
You don't give commands
anymore. little lord.
Please. stop this.
Please stop him.
RODRIK: Hush now. child.
I'm off to see your father.
BRAN: You said
no harm would come!
You said no harm would come.
Theon. please.
Any last words. old man?
Gods help you. Theon Greyjoy.
Now you are truly lost.
BRAN: Theon. please don't.
Do something!
I'll do anything. please!
RICKON: No. please stop it!
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
(BRAN WAILING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(PANTING)
(WIND HOWLING)
JON: Ghost. stay with us.
Ghost!
There goes your pet.
JON: He's not a pet.
QHORIN: No. you're right.
he's not.
You can't tame a wild thing.
You can't trust
a wild thing.
Ghost is different.
So you think.
Wild creatures
have their own rules.
their own reasons.
And you'll never
know them.
Now the wildlings
we're looking for
sleep during the day
and hunt at night.
I thought you said
you couldn't know
wild things.
I said you can't.
They find a nice
cave to hide in
while the sun's up
and do their killing
when it's dark.
We could do the same.
No. we couldn't.
This is their country.
They know where to walk.
where not to walk.
I've lost good men
who fell into a crevasse
they didn't see
till they were in it.
My father always
said I'm of the North.
(CHUCKLES)
I wasn't joking.
Look around. boy.
This look like
home to you?
You start thinking
you know this place.
it will kill you.
You understand me?
No. you don't.
We're at war.
We've always
been at war.
It's never going
to end 'cause we're
not fighting an enemy.
We're fighting
the North. and it's
not going anywhere.
The Watch has
given you a great gift.
You only have
one thing to give
in return.
your life.
I'll gladly give my life.
I don't want you
to be glad about it.
I want you to curse
and fight until your
heart's done pumping.
And know this. boy.
Your death will be
a gift for them
south of the Wall.
They'll never know
what you've done.
They'll never
know how you died.
They won't even
know your damn name.
But they'll be
alive because some
nameless bastard
north of the Wall
gave his life for theirs.
Now. do you understand me?
I do.
You're even dumber
than you look.
It's just words. boy.
to keep us a little
warmer in the night.
Make us feel like
we've got a purpose.
(LAUGHS) Come on.
We've got to find
these goat fuckers
before night falls
and they find us.
TYWIN: Can you read?
My lord?
Can you read?
This letter detailing
our infantry movements
was meant for Lord Damon
of House Marbrand.
It was sent to Lord
Marlyn of House Dormand.
My apologies. my lord.
I must have...
Girl. fetch me
the History of the Greater
and the Lesser Houses.
It's the one on this...
(CHUCKLES)
My cupbearer can
read better than you.
To whom does House Dormand
owe allegiance?
My lord. I...
To the Starks of Winterfell!
Who have 20.000
men and my son!
I judged you might be good
for something more than
brutalizing peasants.
I see I overestimated you.
If you ever put my son's
life at risk again. I'll...
Leave us.
Put the book away. girl.
(DOOR OPENING)
(DOOR CLOSING)
Maybe you should devise
our next battle plan
while you're about it.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(DOOR OPENS)
Lord Petyr Baelish.
Mmm.
Give us the room.
Clear all this.
(DOOR OPENING)
(DOOR CLOSING)
Lord Tywin.
Baelish.
Wine?
Thank you.
What news from the capital?
I traveled here directly
from Renly Baratheon's camp.
Ah. the late King Renly.
Rather a short reign.
Murdered by a woman.
I hear.
So they say.
There has been talk of
other forces at work.
Dark forces.
Here.
(SCOFFS)
Men love to blame
demons when their
grand plans unravel.
It is my belief that
a moment of chaos affords
opportunities lost soon after.
You say that as if
you were the first man
alive to think it.
Yes. a crisis
is an opportunity.
What other brilliant insights
have you brought me today?
After the Lannisters and
the Starks. the Tyrells
command the largest host.
Their lands
are the most fertile
in the Seven Kingdoms.
feeding horses and soldiers.
Yes. yes. yes.
The Tyrells have
not yet declared
for any of
the surviving kings.
Loras wants revenge.
He blames Stannis
for Renly's death.
And Margaery...
Wants to be queen.
Yes. she does.
House Tyrell rebelled
against the Iron Throne.
Against my grandson.
They did.
And perhaps that treason
should be punished
one day.
after Stannis and
Robb Stark are defeated.
More wine for Lord Baelish.
If you will allow me
to represent your
family's interests.
I believe that
an advantageous agreement...
The Tyrell host has
returned to Highgarden?
They have.
(GASPS)
Pardon. my lord.
It's only wine.
You would ride
there yourself?
Tonight. with your leave.
I'll have an answer
by nightfall.
That'll be all. girl.
And what else?
On your son
Tyrion's directive.
I met with Catelyn Stark.
Why?
He had an interesting
proposal for her
concerning her daughters.
Hmm.
(GROANS)
(SHOUTING)
(PANTING)
A girl.
A wildling.
We could question her.
You could.
She won't answer.
I've known a wildling
to bite off his tongue
instead of talking.
What's your name?
Ygritte.
She was reaching
for this ax when
you got to her.
Give her half a chance.
she'll bury it in your face.
I gave you my name.
I'm Jon Snow.
You ought to burn
them you killed.
QHORIN: We'd need
a big fire for that.
Tell me. Ygritte.
Why do you want us
to build a big fire?
Are there some more
friends in the area?
Burn them
or maybe you'll need
those swords again.
Our boy here's
already killed
one dead man.
He can do it
again if he has to.
What waits beyond
the pass?
The free folk.
How many?
(CHUCKLES)
Hundreds and thousands.
More than you've
ever seen. crow.
Why come to the mountains?
What's in the Frostfangs
your king could want?
Do you mean to
march on the Wall?
Do you know who I am. girl?
Qhorin Halfhand.
Tell me true.
If your people captured me.
would they take me prisoner?
They'd take your
head off your shoulders
if they was feeling kind.
If not. they'd kill you slow.
(SIGHS)
We have no food for her.
Can't spare
a man to watch her.
Can't let her go.
She'll bring Mance Rayder's
army down on us.
It needs to be done.
Want me to do it?
JON: No.
No. I'll do it.
Come. brothers.
We'll leave him to it.
We'll meet you at the top.
Don't take too long.
We're deep in
their country now.
You never killed
a woman before. did you?
You don't need to do it.
Mance would take you.
I know he would.
There's secret ways.
The crows would
never catch us.
I'm as much
a crow as they are.
Will you burn me?
After?
Can't.
Someone might see the smoke.
Strike hard and true.
Jon Snow.
or I'll come
back and haunt you.
That's cold.
Go on.
Be quick about it.
Do it.
Bastard. do it!
(GRUNTS)
(CLANGING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
You can't do it.
We both know it.
The sun's going down.
Jon Snow.
And your friends
are nowhere close.
I'll find them.
Call for them. Go on.
Call loudly.
SEPTON: May the Seven
guide the princess
on her journey.
May the Mother
give her health.
May the crone give her wisdom.
May the warrior
give her courage.
(SOBBING)
(SEPTON CONTINUES)
One day I pray
you love someone.
I pray you love her so much.
when you close your eyes.
you see her face.
I want that for you.
I want you to know
what it's like
to love someone.
to truly love someone.
Before I take her from you.
(CONTINUES SPEAKING)
(SOBBING)
You sound like a little cat
mewling for his mother.
Princes don't cry.
I saw you cry.
Did you say something.
my lady?
My little brother cried
when I left Winterfell.
So?
It seems a normal thing.
Is your little
brother a prince?
No.
Not really relevant
then. is it?
Come. dog.
MAN 1: Hail Joffrey!
Hail to the King.
(MAN LAUGHS)
Seven blessings
on you. Your Grace.
MAN 2: Murderer! Bastard!
All hail the King.
MAN 3: He's no king.
He's a bastard!
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
Please. Your Grace.
we're hungry.
(CROWD SHOUTING)
MAN 4: Freak.
Get the Prince
back to the Keep now.
Yes. my lord. Come. quickly.
WOMAN: Please. Your Grace.
give us some food!
MAN 5: Bread.
Your Grace. please!
(GROANS)
(CROWD GASPS)
Who threw that?
I want the man who threw that.
Find who did that
and bring him to me!
GUARD 1: Hold on!
GUARD 2: Hold them back!
JOFFREY: Just kill them!
Kill them all!
(GROANS)
Move. Move!
GUARD 1: Pull back!
MAN 6: Tear him to pieces!
What are you doing?
I want these people
executed!
And they want
the same for you.
(SEPTON SCREAMING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
Where's Sansa?
(SCREAMING)
GUARD 3: Through the door.
GUARD 4: Come on.
Push hard.
(WHIMPERING)
Protect the king!
Get back!
Fall back!
(CROWD SHOUTING)
Keep him safe!
MAN 7: Brotherfucker!
Watch out.
Hold them back.
(WHIMPERS)
Hey.
Traitors!
I'll have all their heads.
You blind. bloody fool.
You can't insult me.
We've had vicious kings
and we've had idiot kings.
but I don't know if we've
ever been cursed with
a vicious idiot for a king.
You can't...
I can. I am.
They attacked me!
They threw a cow pie
at you. so you decided
to kill them all?
They're starving.
you fool.
All because of
a war you started.
You're talking to a king!
(SHRIEKS)
And now I've
struck a king.
Did my hand fall
from my wrist?
Where is the Stark girl?
Let them have her.
If she dies. you'll never
get your Uncle Jaime back.
You owe him quite
a bit. you know.
(PANTING)
(GROANS)
Where are you going?
You ever been fucked.
little girl?
(WHIMPERING)
Come here.
Take some men and go
and find the Stark girl.
I take my orders
from the king.
GUARD 5: Where?
GUARD 6: This way.
(SANSA SOBBING)
Please!
No! No!
(SCREAMING)
(CHOKING)
Please!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
You're all right now.
little bird.
You're all right.
(CROWD SHOUTING)
We'll get you. We'll get you.
This way.
Are you hurt. my lady?
The little bird's bleeding.
Someone take her
back to her cage.
See to that cut.
Well done. Clegane.
I didn't do it for you.
He shouldn't make me wait.
The Spice King is
the second wealthiest
man in Qarth.
He makes everyone wait.
Of course. you could have
avoided this embarrassment
if you married
the wealthiest man
in Qarth.
I already have a husband.
Khal Drogo is gone.
Khaleesi.
You are far too young
to be a widow forever
and far too beautiful.
And you are far too smart
to think that I will
succumb to flattery.
I have traveled
very far in my life
and met many women.
but none that are
immune to flattery.
MAN: The Mother of Dragons!
Here he comes.
Forgive me.
I had terrible
dreams last night.
Terrible dreams.
I could not sleep
until the sun was shining
and the birds were singing.
Look what a beauty you are
now the Red Waste has
been washed off you.
I am sorry about all
that unpleasantness.
The silver hair of
a true Targaryen.
Xaro Xhoan Daxos.
she is far too lovely
for a glorified
dockworker like yourself.
Very true. and yet they say
that your grandfather.
who sold pepper off
the back of a wagon.
married a lady far lovelier
and higher born than himself.
Every lady alive
was lovelier
and higher born
than my grandfather.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Did my servants not offer you
something to eat. to drink?
I'll have them
flogged in the square.
Thank you. my lord.
You are a gracious host.
but there is no servant alive
that can bring me what I want.
Oh. she has a talent
for drama. this one.
So. my little princess.
what is it you want?
My birthright.
The Seven Kingdoms
of Westeros.
I fear I'm no better
than a servant
in this regard.
I cannot give you
what I do not have.
I'm not asking you
for the kingdoms.
I'm asking you for ships.
I need to cross
the Narrow Sea.
I need my ships as well.
I use them. you see.
to bring spices from
one port to another.
Whatever you grant
me now will be repaid
three times over when
I retake the Iron Throne.
Retake?
Did you once sit
on the Iron Throne?
My father sat there.
before he was murdered.
But if you did not
sit on it yourself.
would it not be
correct to say
"take the Iron Throne"?
I didn't come here
to argue grammar.
Of course not.
You came to take my ships.
So let me explain
my position.
little princess.
Unlike you. I do not
have exalted ancestors.
I make my living by trade.
And I judge every
trade on its merits.
You ask for ships.
You say I shall
be repaid triple.
I do not doubt your honesty
or your intentions.
But before you
repay your debts.
you must seize
the Seven Kingdoms.
Do you have an army?
Not yet.
You do not have an army.
Do you have powerful
allies in Westeros?
There are many there
that support my claim.
When were you there last?
I left when I was a baby.
So. in truth.
you have no allies.
The people will rise
to fight for their rightful
queen when I return.
Ah.
Forgive me. little princess.
but I cannot
make an investment
based on wishes and dreams.
Now if you'll pardon me.
Do you know Illyrio Mopatis.
Magister of Pentos?
Yes. we've met.
A shrewd man.
For my wedding. he gave me
three petrified dragon eggs.
He believed... The world
believed that the ages
had turned them to stone.
How many centuries
has it been since dragons
roamed the skies?
But I dreamt that if
I carried those eggs
into a great fire.
they would hatch.
When I stepped into
the fire. my own people
thought I was mad.
But when the fire burned out.
I was unhurt.
the Mother of Dragons.
Do you understand?
I'm no ordinary woman.
My dreams come true.
I admire your passion.
But in business. I trust
in logic. not passion.
I'm sorry. little princess.
I am not your
little princess.
I am Daenerys Stormborn
of the blood of Old Valyria.
and I will take what is mine.
With fire and blood.
I will take it.
Yes. my lady.
but not with my ships.
Who taught you to read?
My father. my lord.
Hmm.
I taught my son Jaime to read.
The maester
came to me one day.
told me he wasn't learning.
He couldn't make
sense of the letters.
He reversed them in his head.
The maester said
he'd heard tell
of this affliction
and that we simply
must accept it.
Ha!
After that. I sat Jaime down
for four hours every
day until he learned.
He hated me for it.
for a time.
For a long time.
But he learned.
Hmm.
Where is your father?
Is he alive?
Who was he?
A stonemason.
A stonemason who could read?
Hmm.
He taught himself.
Quite a man.
What killed him?
Loyalty.
You're a sharp
little thing. aren't you?
Did...
Forgive me. my lord.
I shouldn't ask questions.
No.
But you've already begun.
Did you know your father.
my lord?
I did.
I grew up with him.
I watched him grow old.
He loved us.
He was a good man.
but a weak man.
A weak man who
nearly destroyed
our house and name.
I'm cold.
I'll fetch more wood
for the fire. my lord.
Mmm.
(HORSE WHINNIES)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
Where are you going. girl?
The armory. my lord.
Why?
Lord Tywin sent me.
What might this be?
Lord Tywin gave it to me.
What for?
To take to the armory.
Why would he do that?
Let's go and ask him.
Move!
Get out of the way!
(MEN CHATTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Amory Lorch.
A girl has named
a second name.
A man will do
what must be done.
Now!
A girl cannot tell a man
when exactly he must
do a thing.
A man cannot make a thing
happen before its time.
But he's going to tell Tywin.
He's getting away.
It has to be now.
(SIGHS)
Guard!
Your Grace.
My honor. Your Grace.
Quent.
Lady Talisa.
Your Grace.
I'm not sure I'm a lady.
Westerosi customs are
still a bit foreign to me.
It's hard to keep
all the rules straight.
But if I remember my lessons.
a woman of noble birth
is always called a lady.
Unless she's a queen
or a princess.
I could find
someone who knows.
Why are you so sure
I'm of noble birth?
Because it's obvious.
What if I told you my father
sold lace on the Long Bridge.
and my mother. my brother
and I lived with him
above our shop?
I'd call you a liar.
Not very noble to accuse
a lady of dishonesty.
I always thought I
was a brilliant liar.
Better at amputations.
I'm afraid.
Quite a pretty spot.
Will we be here long?
I couldn't really discuss
troop movements with you.
I'm not a spy.
Of course. a spy
would deny being a spy.
You're right.
You've found me out.
I'm writing a letter
to the Lannisters.
"The young wolf
is on the move."
Perhaps you'd join me.
If you've got time.
of course. for. well...
CATELYN: Robb.
Mother.
Mother. this is Lady Talisa.
She's been helping
with the wounded.
She's been very helpful.
Lady Talisa.
Lady Stark.
Lady Talisa...
Maegyr.
Maegyr?
Forgive me. I do not
know this name.
An uncommon name here.
An old name in Volantis.
Excuse me. my lady.
Your Grace.
I've missed you.
Yes. you look
positively forlorn.
You surprised me. that's all.
I didn't think
I'd see you today.
I wish that you were
free to follow your heart.
I know.
You have inherited
your father's
responsibilities.
I'm afraid they
come at a cost.
You are promised
to another.
I know.
A debt that must be paid.
I haven't forgotten.
Your Grace. My lady.
News from Winterfell.
(WIND HOWLING)
Your brothers desert you?
I can tell you
which way to go.
We'll stop here.
Too dark to go
any farther today.
Here? There's no shelter here.
There's no shelter anywhere.
There is... if you know
where to look.
The cold could
kill us both.
If you light a fire...
No fire.
But a fire is...
Have it your way.
We'll stay warmer
if we stay close.
Bet you freeze to
death before I do.
Bet your life.
Think they're out
looking for you?
Yes.
Think they'll find you?
You're brave.
Stupid.
but brave.
We start again at first light.
Get some sleep.
Stop moving.
I'm just trying
to get comfortable.
Stop it!
You're still moving.
Was I?
I didn't notice that time.
This cannot be true.
We've had ravens
from White Harbor.
Barrowton and the Dreadfort.
I'm afraid it is true.
Why? Why would Theon...
Because the Greyjoys
are treasonous whores.
My brothers?
We've heard nothing of them.
(SIGHS)
But Rodrik Cassel is dead.
I told you.
never trust a Greyjoy!
I must go north at once.
There's still a war
to win. Your Grace.
How can I call myself king
if I can't hold my own castle?
How can I ask men to
follow me if I can't...
You are a king.
And that means you don't have
to do everything yourself.
Let me go and talk to Theon.
There will be no talk.
He will die for this.
Theon holds the castle
with a skeleton crew.
Let me send word
to my bastard
at the Dreadfort.
He can raise a few hundred
men and retake Winterfell
before the new moon.
We have the Lannisters
on the run.
If you march all
the way back north now.
you'll lose what you gained.
My boy would be honored
to bring you
Prince Theon's head.
Tell your son Bran and
Rickon's safety is paramount.
And Theon. I want him
brought to me alive.
I want to look him in
the eye and ask him why.
And then I'll take
his head myself.
Why on earth
would I trust the word
of a lying little
savage like you?
I'm no liar.
All wildlings are
liars and savages
with no loyalty to
anything or anyone.
I done what I had
to do to stay alive.
I hate the Starks
as well as you do.
Let me serve you. my lord.
How? And don't tell me
to put a spear in your hand.
There are other
ways to serve. my lord.
I'm a prince now.
and you'd do well...
There are other ways
to serve. my prince.
(CHUCKLES)
Like what?
We know things.
the free people.
You know things?
Like what?
How to eat dirt? (LAUGHS)
(SCOFFS)
Other things.
Savage things.
Wait outside.
I always wondered
what you had under there.
It comes at a price.
I'm not killing you.
That's your price.
I already had that.
What do you want then.
other than your
miserable life?
What all free people want.
My freedom.
Well. you shall have it. then.
But only if you serve me well.
Ow!
Shh.
It's not deep.
I thought they were
going to kill me.
They thought so. too.
He hated me.
the man who hit me.
I saw it in his eyes.
Hated me.
He never met me before.
but he wanted to hurt me.
Of course he did.
Why? Why would a stranger...
You are everything
he will never have.
Your horse eats better
than his children.
It doesn't matter now.
He's dead.
I would have given
them bread if I had it.
I hate the king
more than any of them.
Don't say these things.
If the wrong
people hear you...
But you're not
the wrong people.
Don't trust anybody.
Life is safer that way.
(MURMURS)
And where are you going?
I have something for you
from Prince Theon.
What?
Me.
He says I'm to make
the rounds.
And keep you warm.
(GROANS)
(WHISTLES)
The Spice King refuses me
because I'm a bad investment.
The Silk King won't
support me because of his
business with the Lannisters.
Why offend
his best customer?
And the Copper King
offers me a single ship
on the condition that I lie
with him for a night.
Does he think I will
whore myself for a boat?
When I came to this city.
I had nothing.
Truly nothing.
I slept by the docks.
And when I could find
work loading the ships.
I would eat.
If not. I dreamed of food.
Today. I am
the richest man
in Qarth.
Do you think the path
from poverty to wealth is
always pure and honorable?
I have done many things.
Khaleesi.
that a righteous
man would condemn.
And here I am.
with no regrets.
Bar the gates.
Ring the bells.
Slowly. Khaleesi.
(BELLS TOLLING)
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
DAENERYS: Where are they?
Where are my dragons?
(DRAGONS SCREECHING)
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-